Dean Blinder





Software and Information Engineering graduate at Ben Gurion University. Work experience at Wix.com company as a Mobile Developer (React Native and TypeScript). Working closely with the product manager and UX designer. Experience in-site and off-site communication, good team player, and independent.

Experience

Jun 2021 – today: Mobile Developer, Wix.com

- Developing the Owner App by Wix with React Native and TypeScript, an application that serves more than 1 Million users around the world.
- Working close to the product manager, UX designer and back-end engineers.
- Write scalable code using best practices and principles.
- Work as a part of a team, independently and with other teams around the world.
- TDD developing.

2010 - 2013: IT, Recruiting Station, IDF

- Inspected and upgraded user's computer networking systems. updated software and replaced outdated hardware, including desktop PCs, laptops, routers, and ethernet cables.
- Graduating SAP implementation course and implementing it in the base.
- Instructed new software features for system users.

Education

2017 – 2022: B.Sc. Information Software Engineering, Ben Gurion University.

1998 – 2010: The Hebrew Reali School in Haifa. (Extended courses: computer science)

Projects

- Application, responsive to mobile and PC (react.js)
 - An application targeted at assisting users during the pandemic. People can upload a grocery list request. Anyone who wishes to assist can view the requests on the map with details and contact the requester directly through WhatsApp and Facebook using google maps API, react.js and firebase. video link, GitHub link.
- React Native hitchhiking Mobile App. in progress developing Mobile App, anyone can request a ride from anywhere to anywhere.

Skills

Programming Languages: React Native | React.js | TypeScript | JavaScript | Python | Java | Vue.js | SQL | Object-Oriented | OPP | node.js | TDD | Firebase.

Languages

Hebrew, native | English, fluent.